Guide to the Burney Family Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Burney Family Collection, Series I
  - REEVES, JOHN, CA. 1752-1829
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Jan 20 (Box 14, Folder 1059)
  - RENNIE, JOHN, 1761-1821
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809 May 9 (Box 14, Folder 1060)
  - REYNOLDS, FRANCES
    - Letter to Charlotte Ann (Burney) Broome, [1797] Jul 3 (Box 14, Folder 1061)
  - RICHARDS, JOHN INIGO
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805 Oct 22 (Box 14, Folder 1062)
  - RICHMOND, GEORGE, 1809-1896
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1876, 1877 (Box 14, Folder 1063)
  - RICHMOND, JOHN
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1874 Jan 26 (Box 14, Folder 1064)
  - RICKMAN, THOMAS, 1776-1841
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1834-37 (Box 14, Folder 1065)
  - RIGAUD, STEPHEN POTTER, 1774-1839
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1838 Mar 11 (Box 14, Folder 1066)
  - RIOLLAY, FRANCIS, 1748-1797
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1785?] (Box 14, Folder 1067)
  - RIOLLAY, MRS. M.
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1792 (Box 14, Folder 1068)
  - ROBERTS, DAVID, 1796-1864
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1832 Jun 4 (Box 14, Folder 1069)
  - ROBINSON, HENRY, CRABB, 1775-1867
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1839 Sep (Box 14, Folder 1070)
  - ROBSON, GEORGE FENNELL, 1788-1833
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1830 May 19 (Box 14, Folder 1071)
  - ROGERS, SAMUEL, 1763-1855
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806-[13] (Box 14, Folder 1072)
  - RONCAGLIO, FRANCESCO
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1778 (Box 14, Folder 1073)
  - ROSE, HENRY JOHN, 1800-1873
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1841 Oct 5 (Box 14, Folder 1074)
  - ROSE, HUGH
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809 Feb 5 (Box 14, Folder 1075)
  - ROSE, HUGH JAMES, 1795-1838
    - Letter to Alexander d'Arblay, [ca. 1818] (Box 14, Folder 1076)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1820, 1827 (Box 14, Folder 1077)
  - ROSE, SAMUEL, 1767-1804
    - Letter to Rosette Burney, 1783 Oct 9 (Box 14, Folder 1078)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1787] (Box 14, Folder 1079)
  - ROSE, WILLIAM, 1719-1786
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1784, 1785 (Box 15, Folder 1080)
  - ROSSE, LAWRENCE PARSONS, 2ND EARL OF, 1758-1841
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812 Sep 7 (Box 15, Folder 1081)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1823 Jan 26 (Box 15, Folder 1082)
  - ROUTH, MARTIN JOSEPH, 1755-1854
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790-1808 (Box 15, Folder 1083)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1818-1837 (Box 15, Folder 1084)
  - ROYAL INSTITUTION OF GREAT BRITAIN, LONDON
    - Certificate of membership for Charles Burney, D.D., 1803 Jan 17 (Box 15, Folder 1085)
  - RUDING, ROGERS, 1751-1820
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1817 Jan 31 (Box 15, Folder 1086)
  - RUSSELL, F.
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1087)
  - RYLE, JOHN CHARLES, BISHOP OF LIVERPOOL, 1816-1900
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1887 May 21 (Box 15, Folder 1088)
  - [SARTON, M. P.]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1889 Mar 27 (Box 15, Folder 1089)
  - SASS, HENRY, 1788-1824
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1826 Dec 19 (Box 15, Folder 1090)
  - SCHUBACH, [JACOB]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1779 Sep (Box 15, Folder 1091)
  - SCOTT, ROBERT, 1811-1887
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1874 Jan 20 (Box 15, Folder 1092)
  - SCOTT, THOMAS
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1829 Nov 12 (Box 15, Folder 1093)
  - SCOTT, WILL[IAM]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1831 Jun 5 (Box 15, Folder 1094)
  - SEALE, [JOHN BARLOW, 1753-1838]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1789 Nov 19 (Box 15, Folder 1095)
  - SEDGWICK, ADAM, 1785-1873
    - Letter to Charlotte [Mrs. Henry] Barrett, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1096)
  - SWLBOURNE, ROUNDELL PALMER, 1ST EARL OF, 1812-1895
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1886 (Box 15, Folder 1097)
  - SELWYN, GEORGE AUGUSTUS, 1719-1791
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1785] Dec 5 (Box 15, Folder 1098)
  - SELWYN, JOHN RICHARDSON, BISHOP OF MELANESIA
    [1844-1898]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1894 Oct 31 (Box 15, Folder 1099)
  - SELWYN, WILLIAM, 1806-1875
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1873 Dec 19 (Box 15, Folder 1100)
  - SEWARD, WILLIAM, 1747-1799
    - Letter to Fanny d'Arblay, 1779 (Box 15, Folder 1101)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [ca. 1792]-[pre 1799], n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1102)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790-[ca. 1791] (Box 15, Folder 1103)
  - SEYMOUR, GEORGE FRANKLIN, BISHOP OF SPRINGFIELD
    [1829-1906]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1897 Jun 22 (Box 15, Folder 1104)
  - SHARP, RICHARD, 1759-1855
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [pre-1791?] (Box 15, Folder 1105)
  - SHARP, WILLIAM, 1749-1824
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804, 1810 (Box 15, Folder 1106)
  - SHEPHERD, GEORGE
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], 1845 Sep 8 (Box 15, Folder 1107)
  - SHERIDAN, ELIZABETH ANN (LINLEY)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1108)
  - SHERIDAN, THOMAS
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [post 1800]-14 (Box 15, Folder 1109)
  - SHIELD, WILLIAM, 1748-1829
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1817 Aug 1 (Box 15, Folder 1110)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1827 Mar (Box 15, Folder 1111)
  - SIDDONS, WILLIAM
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Jan 30 (Box 15, Folder 1112)
  - SIDMOUTH, HENRY ADDINGTON, 1ST VISCOUNT, 1757-1844
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807, 1812 (Box 15, Folder 1113)
  - SINCLAIR, SIR JOHN, BART., 1754-1835
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Apr 28 (Box 15, Folder 1114)
    - Letter to Marianne Francis, 1818 Jun 21 (Box 15, Folder 1115)
  - SMELT, LEONARD, 1719?-1800
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1774 Aug 29 (Box 15, Folder 1116)
  - SMITH, ANKER, 1759-1819
    - Receipt, signed, to Charles Burney (Box 15, Folder 1117)
      - D.D., 1802 May 9
  - SMITH, CHARLOTTE (TURNER), 1749-1806
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1793 (Box 15, Folder 1118)
  - SOANE, SIR JOHN, 1753-1837
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Apr 24 (Box 15, Folder 1119)
  - SOCIETY OF SCHOOLMASTERS
    - Resolutions on the death of Charles Burney, D.D., 1818 Feb 14 (Box 15, Folder 1120)
    - Song of the Deipnosophists, 1836 Dec 17 (Box 15, Folder 1121)
  - SOUTHEY, ROBERT, 1774-1843
    - Letters to Charlotte Ann (Burney) Francis Broome, 1829 (Box 15, Folder 1122)
  - SPAIN, AMBASSADOR OF
    - Invitation to Frances (Burney) D'Arblay, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1123)
  - SPENCE, N. D. M.
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1886 Nov 18 (Box 15, Folder 1124)
  - SPENCER, AUBREY GEORGE, BISHOP OF JAMAICA
    [1795-1872]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1844 Aug 5 (Box 15, Folder 1125)
  - SPENCER, GEORGE JOHN, 2ND EARL, 1758-1834
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1803-10 (Box 15, Folder 1126)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1812-17 (Box 15, Folder 1127)
  - SPENCER, LAVINIA (BINGHAM) SPENCER, COUNTESS
    [1762-1831]
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Dec 3 (Box 15, Folder 1128)
  - SPENCER, WILLIAM ROBERT, 1769-1834
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805 Jun 28 (Box 15, Folder 1129)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1824] May 29 (Box 15, Folder 1130)
  - STAEL-HOLSTEIN, ANNE LOUISE GERMAINE (NECKER)
    [baronne de, 1766-1817]
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, [1793] Sep 2 (Box 15, Folder 1131)
  - STANLEY, ARTHUR PENRHYN, 1813-1881
    - Letter to [Charles Burney IV], 1872 Nov (Box 15, Folder 1132)
  - STEEVENS, GEORGE, 1736-1800
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1796 Feb 19 (Box 15, Folder 1133)
  - STOCKDALE, PERCIVAL, 1736-1811
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1788 Jan 23 (Box 15, Folder 1134)
  - STONHOUSE, SIR JAMES, 1716-1795
    - Letter to Charles Burney, 1795 Jan 15 (Box 15, Folder 1135)
  - STOWELL, WILLIAM SCOTT, BARON, 1745-1836
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1790 Jan 15] (Box 15, Folder 1136)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1790 [Jun?] 15 (Box 15, Folder 1137)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807-17 (Box 15, Folder 1138)
  - STRANGE, J.
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798 Mar 27 (Box 15, Folder 1139)
  - SUARD, JEAN BAPTISTE ANTOINE, 1734-1817
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [ca. 1774-76] (Box 15, Folder 1140)
  - SUMNER, CHARLES RICHARD, BISHOP OF WINCHESTER
    [1790-1874]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1834 Dec 22 (Box 15, Folder 1141)
  - TAIT, ARCHIBALD CAMPBELL, ARCHBISHOP OF
    [Canterbury, 1811-1882]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1881 Jul 22 (Box 15, Folder 1142)
  - TATE, JAMES, 1771-1843
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1824-1832 (Box 15, Folder 1143)
  - TAYLOR, TOM, 1817-1880
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1878 Jul 17 (Box 15, Folder 1144)
  - TEMPLE, FREDERICK, ARCHBISHOP OF CANTERBURY
    [1821-1902]
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1891 May 18 (Box 15, Folder 1145)
  - TENDUCCI, GIUSTO FERNANDO
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [ca. 1790?] (Box 15, Folder 1146)
  - THOMAS, JOSIAH, 1760-1820
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799-1817 (Box 15, Folder 1147)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1805-[post 1809] (Box 15, Folder 1148)
  - THOMOND, MARY (PALMER) O'BRIEN, MARCHIONESS
    [1750-1820]
    - Letter to [Charles Burney, Mus.D.], [post 1807] May 23 (Box 15, Folder 1149)
  - TO BURNEY AT GREENWICH
    - Manuscript in an unknown hand, [post 1790] (Box 15, Folder 1150)
  - TODD, HENRY JOHN, 1763-1825
    - Letters to Charles Burney D.D., 1801-10 (Box 15, Folder 1151)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1807-12?] (Box 15, Folder 1152)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, [1810]-[26] (Box 15, Folder 1153)
    - Letter to the Rev. G. A. Hatch, 1806 Jul 6 (Box 15, Folder 1154)
  - TOMLINE, SIR GEORGE PRETYMAN, BISHOP OF
    [Winchester, 1750-1827]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1801-11 (Box 15, Folder 1155)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1816 (Box 15, Folder 1156)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1817 (Box 15, Folder 1157)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1818-[20] (Box 15, Folder 1158)
  - TOWNSHEND, GEORGE TOWNSHEND, 1ST MARQUIS
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1773 Aug 22 (Box 15, Folder 1159)
  - TRAVERS, BENJAMIN, 1783-1858
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1160)
    - Letter to Frances Bentley (Young) Burney, 1822 Jul 24 (Box 15, Folder 1161)
  - TROLLOPE, ANTHONY, 1815-1882
    - Letter to Charles Edward Burney, 1865 Nov 26 (Box 15, Folder 1162)
    - Letter to Gibbon, 1860 Jul 24 (Box 15, Folder 1163)
  - TROLLOPE, ARTHUR WILLIAM, 1768-1827
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1823 Sep 30 (Box 15, Folder 1164)
  - TROWER, MRS. E.
    - Letter to Margaret Anne Burney, [ca. 1865] (Box 16, Folder 1165)
  - TURNER, ALFRED
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1838 Nov 8 (Box 16, Folder 1166)
  - TURNER, DAWSON, 1775-1858
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1824 Feb 16 (Box 16, Folder 1167)
  - TURTON, THOMAS, 1735-1804
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1830-45 (Box 16, Folder 1168)
  - TWINING, THOMAS, 1735-1804
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [post 1775 Dec 24] (Box 16, Folder 1169)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1787 Apr 28 (Box 16, Folder 1170)
    - Copy of a letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1789 Sep 2 (Box 16, Folder 1171)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1789-90 (Box 16, Folder 1172)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799 (Box 16, Folder 1173)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1803 (Box 16, Folder 1174)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809-17 (Box 16, Folder 1175)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1818-33 (Box 16, Folder 1176)
  - TWISS, HORACE, 1787-1849
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Oct 3 (Box 16, Folder 1177)
  - TWISS, RICHARD, 1747-1821
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [ca. 1774] (Box 16, Folder 1178)
  - TYRWHITT, THOMAS, 1730-1786
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1780-82] (Box 16, Folder 1179)
  - VAN MILDERT, WILLIAM, BISHOP OF DURHAM
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1816 Jul 2 (Box 16, Folder 1180)
  - VINCENT, WILLIAM, 1739-1815
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798-1806 (Box 16, Folder 1181)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807-13 (Box 16, Folder 1182)
  - WACE, HENRY, 1836-1924
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1884 Feb 29 (Box 16, Folder 1183)
  - WADDINGTON, GEORGIANA MARY ANN (PORT)
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1795 Sep 25 (Box 16, Folder 1184)
  - WALKER, JOSEPH COOPER, 1761-1810
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1796-98 (Box 16, Folder 1185)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1799-1806 (Box 16, Folder 1186)
  - WARREN, SIR THOMAS HERBERT, 1853-1930
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1901 Mar 5 (Box 16, Folder 1187)
  - WARRINGTON, THOMAS
    - Letter to Charles Burney V, 1905 Oct 22 (Box 16, Folder 1188)
  - WARTON, JOSEPH, 1722-1800
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1783-1790 (Box 16, Folder 1189)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1792-1796 (Box 16, Folder 1190)
  - WEDDELL, E.
    - Letter to [Charles Parr Burney], [post 1813] Jan 22 (Box 16, Folder 1191)
  - WESLEY, SAMUEL, 1766-1837
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1799-1808], n.d. (Box 16, Folder 1192)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1809-10 (Box 16, Folder 1193)
  - WESTON, STEPHEN, 1747-1830
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1816 Sep 1 (Box 16, Folder 1194)
  - WHIFFIN, W.
    - Receipt to Charles Burney, D.D. and B. Bland Kelley, 1816 Mar 21 (Box 16, Folder 1195)
  - WHITCOMBE, W. G.
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1828 Jan 2 (Box 16, Folder 1196)
  - WHITE, JOSEPH, 1745-1814
    - Agreement with Charles Burney and Richard Porson, 1789 Sep 5 (Box 16, Folder 1197)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799 Mar 20 (Box 16, Folder 1198)
  - WHITE, RICHARD WALTON, 1784-1855
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1825 Jan 21 (Box 16, Folder 1199)
  - WHITE, THOMAS HOLT, 1763-1841
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1826 Dec 1 (Box 16, Folder 1200)
  - WHITWORTH, SIR CHARLES, 1714?-1778
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1774] (Box 16, Folder 1201)
  - WIGHT, OSBORNE, B. 1753
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1792 Feb 16 (Box 16, Folder 1202)
  - WIGRAM, JOSEPH COTTON, BISHOP OF ROCHESTER
    [1798-1867]
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1860 May, Sep (Box 16, Folder 1203)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1861 May, Jul (Box 16, Folder 1204)
    - Letter to Frances Bentley (Young) Burney, 1865 Jul 14 (Box 16, Folder 1205)
  - WILBERFORCE, SAMUEL, BISHOP OF WINCHESTER
    [1805-1873]
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, [1870]-73 (Box 16, Folder 1206)
  - WILBERFORCE, WILLIAM, 1759-1833
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, 1818, 1822 (Box 16, Folder 1207)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813, 1814 (Box 16, Folder 1208)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1821 Mar 1 (Box 16, Folder 1209)
    - Letters to Marianne Francis, 1816-19, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 1210)
  - WILBRAHAM, ROGER, 1743-1829
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807-14 (Box 16, Folder 1211)
  - WILD, CHARLES
    - Letter to Frances Bentley (Young) Burney, [1826 Dec] (Box 16, Folder 1212)
  - WILKIE, SIR DAVID, 1785-1841
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1814 Jul 31 (Box 16, Folder 1213)
  - WILKINSON, THOMAS EDWARD, D. 1914
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1877 Apr 12 (Box 16, Folder 1214)
  - WILLIAMS, DAVID, 1786-1860
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1824, 1854 (Box 16, Folder 1215)
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, 1851 Dec 6 (Box 16, Folder 1216)
  - WILLIS, THOMAS
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1816 Jul 5 (Box 16, Folder 1217)
  - WILLS, SIR ALFRED, 1828-1912
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1886 May (Box 16, Folder 1218)
  - WILSON, JOHN, 1785-1854
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1814 Apr 3 (Box 16, Folder 1219)
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, [1820]-21 (Box 16, Folder 1220)
  - WILSON, PATRICK
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1811 Apr 19 (Box 16, Folder 1221)
  - WINDHAM, WILLIAM, 1750-1810
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1787]-94 (Box 16, Folder 1222)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1791 Jul 28 (Box 16, Folder 1223)
  - WINSTANLEY, THOMAS, 1749-1823
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790 May 25 (Box 16, Folder 1224)
  - WOLLASTON, FRANCIS, 1731-1815
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1786 Feb 3 (Box 16, Folder 1225)
  - WOLVERTON, GEORGE GRENFELL, 2ND BARON, 1824-1887
    - Letter to Charles Burney IV, [1885 Jul 23] (Box 16, Folder 1226)
  - WOOD, FRANCES ANNE (BURNEY), 1812-1860
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1824, 1827 (Box 16, Folder 1227)
    - Letter to Frances Bentley (Young) Burney, 1825 Apr 15 (Box 16, Folder 1228)
  - WOOD, ROSETTA D'ARBLAY
    - Letter to [Charles Burney IV], 1902 Dec 24 (Box 16, Folder 1229)
  - WOODFALL, GEORGE, 1767-1824
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1817 Nov 26 (Box 16, Folder 1230)
  - WOODFORD, JAMES RUSSELL, BISHOP OF ELY, 1820-1885
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1875 (Box 16, Folder 1231)
  - WORDSWORTH, CHRISTOPHER, BISHOP OF LINCOLN
    [1807-1885]
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1844 Oct 10 (Box 16, Folder 1232)
  - WROUGHTON, RICHARD, 1748-1822
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1804 Dec 26 (Box 16, Folder 1233)
  - WYATT, JAMES, 1746-1813
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1806 Jan 16 (Box 16, Folder 1234)
  - WYON, WILLIAM, 1795-1851
    - Letter to Charles Parr Burney, 1833 Dec 10 (Box 16, Folder 1235)
  - YEATMAN-BIGGS, HUYSHE WOLCOTT, BISHOP OF COVENTRY
    [1845-1922]
    - Letters to Charles Burney IV, 1897, 1904 (Box 16, Folder 1236)
  - YOUNG, ARTHUR, 1741-1820
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1789-97 (Box 16, Folder 1237)
  - YOUNG, DOROTHY
    - Letter to Frances Burney d'Arblay, [1771] Feb 26 (Box 16, Folder 1238)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1795-[96] (Box 16, Folder 1239)
  - YOUNG, JAMES
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798 Aug 13 (Box 16, Folder 1240)
  - YOUNG, JOHN, CA. 1750-1820
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1790-92 (Box 16, Folder 1241)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1793-94 (Box 16, Folder 1242)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798 Apr-Jun (Box 16, Folder 1243)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798 Jul (Box 16, Folder 1244)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798 Aug (Box 16, Folder 1245)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798 Sep-Oct (Box 16, Folder 1246)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1798 Nov-Dec (Box 16, Folder 1247)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799 Jan-Feb (Box 16, Folder 1248)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799 Mar-May (Box 16, Folder 1249)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1799 Jun-[Dec] (Box 16, Folder 1250)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., ca. 1800 Jan-[Apr] (Box 16, Folder 1251)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1800 Jul-Oct (Box 16, Folder 1252)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [ca. 1800-1805] (Box 16, Folder 1253)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1801 Jan-Feb (Box 16, Folder 1254)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1801 Mar (Box 17, Folder 1255)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1801 Apr-Aug (Box 17, Folder 1256)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1801 Nov-Dec (Box 17, Folder 1257)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1802] (Box 17, Folder 1258)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802 Jan-Apr (Box 17, Folder 1259)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., [1802 May] (Box 17, Folder 1260)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802 May (Box 17, Folder 1261)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., [1802 Jun] (Box 17, Folder 1262)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1802 Aug-Dec (Box 17, Folder 1263)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1803 Mar-Nov (Box 17, Folder 1264)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Feb-Mar (Box 17, Folder 1265)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Apr (Box 17, Folder 1266)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 [May 27] (Box 17, Folder 1267)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Jun-Sep (Box 17, Folder 1268)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1804 Oct (Box 17, Folder 1269)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805 Feb-Apr (Box 17, Folder 1270)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1805 May-Dec (Box 17, Folder 1271)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Jan-May (Box 17, Folder 1272)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Jun-Sep (Box 17, Folder 1273)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Oct (Box 17, Folder 1274)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1806 Nov-Dec (Box 17, Folder 1275)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Jan-Mar (Box 17, Folder 1276)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1807 Jun-Oct (Box 17, Folder 1277)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Jan-Apr (Box 17, Folder 1278)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 May-Aug (Box 17, Folder 1279)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1808 Oct (Box 17, Folder 1280)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809 Mar-Apr (Box 17, Folder 1281)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1809 May-Sep (Box 17, Folder 1282)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Feb-May (Box 17, Folder 1283)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Jun-Aug (Box 17, Folder 1284)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1810 Oct-Nov (Box 17, Folder 1285)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1811 Jul-Aug (Box 17, Folder 1286)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1813, 1814 (Box 17, Folder 1287)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1815 Jan-Aug (Box 17, Folder 1288)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1815 Sep-Dec (Box 17, Folder 1289)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., 1816, 1817 (Box 17, Folder 1290)
    - Letters to Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. (Box 17, Folder 1291)
    - Letters to Charles Parr Burney, 1818 Jan, Oct (Box 17, Folder 1292)
  - ZENOBIC, COUNT
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., 1816 Feb 25 (Box 17, Folder 1293)
- Burney Family Collection Additions, Series II
  - HAWKESWORTH, JOHN
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1769 Apr 2 (Box 18, Folder 1294)
  - ARBLAY, FANNY BURNEY D'
    - Manuscript of the title page and Preface to Evelina (Box 18, Folder 1295)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1296)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1297)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1298)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1299)
    - Letter to [Thomas Lowndes?], [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1300)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1301)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1302)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1303)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1304)
    - Letter to Thomas Lowndes, [ca. 1778-80] (Box 18, Folder 1305)
  - PIOZZI, HESTER LYNCH (SALUSBURY) THRALE, 1743-1821
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1778 [Jul] 22 (Box 18, Folder 1306)
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, [ca. 1779-82] (Box 18, Folder 1307)
  - EARLE, W. W.
    - Copy of statement alleging that Dr. Johnson had "corrected" Evelina, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1308)
  - SEWARD, WILLIAM
    - Letter to Charles Burney, D.D., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1309)
  - QUIN, H.
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1788 Jul 16 (Box 18, Folder 1310)
  - HARRIS, JAMES
    - Letter (in third person) to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1775 May 9 (Box 18, Folder 1311)
    - Letter to Francis Wingrave, 1780 Sep 14 (Box 18, Folder 1312)
  - PIOZZI, HESTER LYNCH (SALUSBURY) THRALE, 1743-1821
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1778] Nov 21 (Box 18, Folder 1313)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., [1778 Oct] (Box 18, Folder 1314)
  - MORE, HANNAH
    - Letter to Fanny Burney, n.y. Jul 4 (Box 18, Folder 1315)
  - PACCHIEROTTI, GASPARO, 1744-1821
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., 1786 Oct 30 (Box 18, Folder 1316)
    - Letter to Charles Burney, Mus.D., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1317)